<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Toowoomba West Anglican Parish</title>
    <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Toowoomba West Anglican Parish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.toowoombawest.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pew Sheet 20th June 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/post/pewsheet7321/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.toowoombawest.org/post/pewsheet7321/</guid>
      <description>Sentence  Like living stones, let yourselves be built into a spiritual house, to be a holy priesthood, to offer spiritual sacrifices acceptable to God through Jesus Christ.
 Prayer of the Day  Bountiful God, to whose glory we celebrate the dedication of this house of prayer: we praise you for the many blessings you have given to those who worship here, and we pray that all who seek you in this place may find you, and being filled with the Holy Spirit may become a living temple acceptable to you, through Jesus Christ our Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tazie</title>
      <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/post/tazie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.toowoombawest.org/post/tazie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are the dates for Tazie service, A service of Prayer, Silence and Song&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible Study</title>
      <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/post/bible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.toowoombawest.org/post/bible/</guid>
      <description>Here are the times, locations for bible studys
In Parish Center  Monday 10am and 2pm Saturday 10am  St Augustine&amp;rsquo;s  Tuesday 10am  173 West Street  Tuesday 7pm  M: 0407676917 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.toowoombawest.org/resources/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of the Pastoral services that the church can offer BAPTISM  Baptisms are performed at our regular Sunday services.
If you or a member of your family would like to be baptised, we&amp;rsquo;d love to talk to you about the process.
As a part of the process leading up to Baptism we would ask that you attend a church service and a preparation meeting following the service on the first Sunday of the month (Unless otherwise arranged with the Parish Priest).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.toowoombawest.org/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving</title>
      <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/give/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.toowoombawest.org/give/</guid>
      <description>How to Give in These Troubled Times,
A letter from Rev. Pauline
To Our Supporters of Toowoomba West Anglican Parish. Many of you have made contact re. parish giving. The best way in which you can help your church is to continue to give. This may mean switching to online banking or direct banking. Bank details are as follows: Banking details: BSB 704 901 Account no 00001310 An easier alternative is to Click the link below for direct link via ANFIN, the Diocese financial department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.toowoombawest.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome  At St Alban&amp;rsquo;s Church Newtown and at St Augustine’s Rockville we are more than just a church, we are a community of people who come together to worship, learn, share &amp;amp; give in the name of God.
Why not be part of something special?
There are many different activities to be involved in with church services, baptisms bible studies, weddings, funerals, fundraisers, and of course our famous Teapot Extravaganza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.toowoombawest.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.toowoombawest.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Parish Office,
St Alban&amp;rsquo;s Church &amp;amp; Hall
85-83 Hill St, Newtown, Toowoomba, 4350 QLD Australia
​Office Hours: 9:00 am to 1:00 pm
Wednesday &amp;amp; Thursday
Phone: 07 4638 5521
Email: admin@toowoombawest.org</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
