<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Toowoomba West Anglican Parish</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Toowoomba West Anglican Parish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pew Sheet 11th July 2021</title>
      <link>/post/ps11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ps11/</guid>
      <description>Sentence  Who shall stand in the Lord’s holy place? Those who have clean hands and pure hearts, who do not lift up their hands to what is false. Psalm 23: 3 - 4
 Prayer of the Day  Eternal God, open our eyes to see your hand at work in the splendour of creation and in the beauty of human life. Help us to cherish the gifts that surround us, to share our blessings with our sisters and brothers, and to experience the joy of life in your presence; through Jesus Christ, our Lord, who lives and reigns with you in the unity of the Holy Spirit, one God for ever and ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pew Sheet 4th July 2021</title>
      <link>/post/pewsheet0421/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pewsheet0421/</guid>
      <description>Sentence  Of Jesus many said, ‘What is this wisdom that has been given to him? What deeds of power are being done by his hands!’ mark 6:2
 Prayer of the Day  O Lord our God, you are always more ready to bestow your good gifts upon us than we are to seek them; and more willing to give than we desire or deserve: in our every need, grant us the first and best of all your gifts, the Spirit who makes us your children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pew Sheet 27th June 2021</title>
      <link>/post/pewsheet27621/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pewsheet27621/</guid>
      <description>Sentence  The steadfast love of the Lord never ceases, his mercies never come to an end; they are new every morning; great is your faithfulness
 Prayer of the Day  O Christ for whom we search, out help when help has failed: give us courage to expose our need and ask to be made whole, that, being touched by you, we may be raised to new life in the power of your name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible Study</title>
      <link>/post/bible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bible/</guid>
      <description>Here are the times, locations for bible studys
In Parish Center  Monday 10am and 2pm Saturday 10am  St Augustine&amp;rsquo;s  Tuesday 10am  173 West Street  Tuesday 7pm  M: 0407676917 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taizé</title>
      <link>/post/tazie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tazie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are the dates for Taizé service, A service of Prayer, Silence and Song&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pew Sheet 20th June 2021</title>
      <link>/post/pewsheet7321/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pewsheet7321/</guid>
      <description>Sentence  Like living stones, let yourselves be built into a spiritual house, to be a holy priesthood, to offer spiritual sacrifices acceptable to God through Jesus Christ.
 Prayer of the Day  Bountiful God, to whose glory we celebrate the dedication of this house of prayer: we praise you for the many blessings you have given to those who worship here, and we pray that all who seek you in this place may find you, and being filled with the Holy Spirit may become a living temple acceptable to you, through Jesus Christ our Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
